Saad Khan

saadan06@gmail.com

03109732360

linkedin.com/in/saad-k-7aba04138

https://saadkhan-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

Summary

I am a computer engineering student. I was passionate about engineering from my childhood. I wanted to build things, wanted to know how things work and how to make them better. I like to solve problems, wheather they are technical or interpersonal.

On the programming side, I have worked on Kali Linux created different python scripts, know a little bit about cyber security(Metasploit,NGrok etc).

I've worked with C++, SQL, POSTGRESQL, ORACLE, PYTHON, HTML,5 CSS3, BOOTRAP, JAVA SCRIPT, DJANGO, CODEIGNITOR, SDL and created many Project, Websites, Games using these skills. I also have good grip on concepts of OOPS, Data Structures and DataBases.

I am also interested in UAVs, Have created some UAV Projects in the past and worked on different Flight Controllers like Pixhawk, Ardupilot, Betaflight, BI Heli, etc.

Nonetheless, I'm always willing to learn more and acquire as many opportunities as possible.

Experience

Y Team Member

Team Invictus
Jul 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

Freelance

Photomath

2019 - Present (3 years 11 months +)

Marketing Intern

GoodSpace
Apr 2022 - Jun 2022 (3 months)

Education



Ghulam Ishaq Khan Institute of Engineering Sciences and Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering 2020 - 2024

Peshawar Model Degree College

Intermediate, Pre-Engineering 2018 - 2020

fazia inter school

2015 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

Figure 8 Winner - IEEE GIK Student Branch

- Astera Data Integration BootCamp Astera Software
- Marketing intern GoodSpace
- Full stack web development and Al with Python (Django) Udemy

Skills

C++ • Python (Programming Language) • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Ruby on Rails • JavaScript • Assembly Language • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Heroku • Cloud Computing

Honors & Awards

Neo 22, Figure 8 Winner - IEEE Neo '22

Feb 2022

we engineered and coded a line follower robot which competed against many different unis of Pakistan and won the first prize. received Both the Sheild and the certificate.